A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 1 FA771
Rockefeller Archive Center
John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 1
1984-2010
Rockefeller Archive Center
John A. Hartford Foundation
FA771
47.5 Cubic Feet 125 document boxes.
Organizational History
The John A. Hartford Foundation (JAHF) was established in 1929 by brothers John and George Hartford, sons of the founder of the Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company (A&P). The foundation is a private, nonpartisan philanthropy dedicated to improving the care of older adults.
For its first several decades, the foundation broadly supported clinical medical research. By 1982, it began to focus solely on geriatric healthcare. In 2015, JAHF paid out $20.2 million on a total of 80 active grants and committed $25.3 million to 24 new grants projects, all focused on the care of older adults.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains Grant Files and associated administrative records.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted.
Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The John A. Hartford Foundation records were donated to RAC by JAHF in 2014. Record transfers to RAC began in 2014 and continue as needed.
Arrangement
Arranged as received.
- Grants, 1984-2010; 1
  Scope and Contents note
  Series 1 contains grant files from 1984 to 2010.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically by grantee.
  - Agency for Healthcare Research and Quality: A.S. Beirman (2000-0182), 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
  - American Academy of Nursing: A. Hinshaw (2000-0168), 2000-2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Academy of Nursing: A. Hinshaw (2000-0168), 2000-2005 (Box 2, Folder 7-10)
  - American Academy of Nursing: T. Gaffney (2000-0168), 2000-2005 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - American Academy of Nursing: T. Gaffney (2000-0168), 2000-2005 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - American Academy of Nursing: P. Franklin (2001-0323), 2001-2006 (Box 3, Folder 13-16)
  - American Academy of Nursing: J. Garde (2004-0077), 2004-2007 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - American Academy of Family Physicians Foundation: G. Warshaw (99-0004), 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 18-24)
  - American Academy of Home Care Physicians: C. Row (2002-0031), 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - American Association of Colleges of Nursing (AACN): G.P. Bednash (2001-0327), 2001-2006 (Box 5, Folder 26-31)
  - American Association of Colleges of Nursing (AACN): G.P. Bednash (2001-0125), 2001-2006 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - American Association of Colleges of Nursing (AACN): G.P. Bednash (2001-0125), 2001-2006 (Box 6, Folder 33-39)
  - American Association of Colleges of Nursing (AACN): G.P. Bednash (2001-0125), 2001-2006 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR): S. Lederman (97-0247), 1997-2001 (Box 7, Folder 41-45)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR): O. van der Willik, (98-0310), 1998-2003 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR): O. van der Willik, (98-0310), 1998-2003 (Box 8, Folder 47-55)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR): O. van der Willik (99-0248), 1999-2005 (Box 9, Folder 56-58)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR): O. van der Willik (2000-0181), 2000-2007 (Box 9, Folder 59-62)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR): O. van der Willik (2000-0181), 2000-2007 (Box 10, Folder 63-69)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR): O. van der Willik (2000-0181), 2000-2007 (Box 11, Folder 70-71)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR): O. van der Willik (2000-0445), 2000-2002 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR): S. Lederman (2002-0257), 2002-2006 (Box 11, Folder 73-74)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): D. Jahnigen (92-0022), 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 75-76)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): W. Hazzard (94-0269), 1994-2001 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): W. Hazzard (94-0269), 1994-2001 (Box 12, Folder 78-84)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): W. Hazzard (94-0269), 1994-2001 (Box 13, Folder 85-89)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): Solomon (96-0298), 1996-2000 (Box 13, Folder 90-92)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): Solomon (96-0298), 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 93-98)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): Solomon (96-0298), 1996-2000 (Box 15, Folder 99-100)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): S. Levine (97-0304), 1997-2003 (Box 15, Folder 101-105)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): S. Levine (97-0304), 1997-2003 (Box 16, Folder 106-111)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): S. Levine (97-0304), 1997-2003 (Box 17, Folder 112-118)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): S. Levine (97-0304), 1997-2003 (Box 18, Folder 119-124)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): Solomon (96-0298), 1996-2000 (Box 18, Folder 125)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): Solomon (96-0298), 1996-2000 (Box 19, Folder 126-133)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): N. E. Lundebjerg (99-0632), 1999-2004 (Box 20, Folder 134-136)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): Solomon (2000-0066), 2000-2006 (Box 20, Folder 137-139)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): Solomon (2000-0066), 2000-2006 (Box 21, Folder 140-145)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): Solomon (2000-0066), 2000-2006 (Box 22, Folder 146-148)
  - American Geriatrics Society (AGS): N. E. Lundebjerg (2002-0046), 2002-2006 (Box 22, Folder 149-150)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges: M. B. Anderson (99-0559), 1999-2005 (Box 23, Folder 151-157)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges: M. B. Anderson (2000-0332), 2000-2003 (Box 23, Folder 158)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges: M. B. Anderson (2000-0332), 2000-2003 (Box 24, Folder 159-163)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges: M. B. Anderson (2001-0201), 2001-2006 (Box 24, Folder 164-166)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges: M. B. Anderson (2001-0201), 2001-2006 (Box 25, Folder 167-170)
  - Association of Directors of Geriatric Academic Programs (ADGAP): D. Reuben (2000-0333), 2000-2008 (Box 25, Folder 171-173)
  - Association of Directors of Geriatric Academic Programs (ADGAP): D. Reuben (2000-0333), 2000-2008 (Box 26, Folder 174-179)
  - Association of Directors of Geriatric Academic Programs (ADGAP): D. Reuben (2000-0333), 2000-2008 (Box 27, Folder 180-181)
  - Association of Directors of Geriatric Academic Programs (ADGAP): W. Hall (2001-0304), 2001-2006 (Box 27, Folder 182-187)
  - Association of Directors of Geriatric Academic Programs (ADGAP): W. Hall (2001-0304), 2001-2006 (Box 28, Folder 188-189)
  - Baylor College of Medicine: R. Luchi (94-0142), 1994-1999 (Box 28, Folder 190-193)
  - Baylor College of Medicine: R. Luchi (94-0142), 1994-1999 (Box 29, Folder 194-196)
  - Baylor College of Medicine: R. Luchi/N. Wilson (96-0201), 1996-2001 (Box 29, Folder 197-200)
  - Baylor College of Medicine: R. Luchi/N. Wilson (96-0201), 1996-2001 (Box 30, Folder 201)
  - Baylor College of Medicine: A. Woods (2000-0444), 2000-2005 (Box 30, Folder 202-205)
  - Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center: L. Lipsitz (2005-0046), 2005-2006 (Box 30, Folder 206-207)
  - Boston Medical Center: R. Silliman (2000-0419), 2000-2005 (Box 31, Folder 208-210)
  - Boston Medical Center: R. Silliman (2005-0054), 2005-2009 (Box 31, Folder 211-213)
  - Buffalo General Foundation: B. Naughton (99-0541), 1999-2003 (Box 31, Folder 214-215)
  - Carle Foundation Hospital: C. Schraeder (97-0111), 1997-2004 (Box 32, Folder 216-223)
  - Columbia University School of Nursing: T. Fulmer (92-0219), 1992-1996 (Box 33, Folder 224-228)
  - Community College of Philadelphia: P. Ironside (2006-0237), 2006-2010 (Box 33, Folder 229-230)
  - Community College of Philadelphia: P. Ironside (2006-0237), 2006-2010 (Box 34, Folder 231)
  - Council on Social Work Education: F. Baskind (2000-0607), 2000-2005 (Box 34, Folder 232-236)
  - Council on Social Work Education: F. Baskind (2000-0607), 2000-2005 (Box 35, Folder 237-239)
  - Dartmouth Medical School: J. Barrett (95-0042), 1992-2001 (Box 35, Folder 240-242)
  - Dartmouth Medical School: J. Barrett (95-0042), 1992-2001 (Box 36, Folder 243-251)
  - Dartmouth Medical School: J. Barrett (95-0042), 1992-2001 (Box 37, Folder 252-259)
  - Dartmouth Medical School: J. Barrett (95-0042), 1992-2001 (Box 38, Folder 260-267)
  - Duke University Medical Center: H. Cohen (97-0205), 1997-2000 (Box 39, Folder 268-269)
  - Duke University Medical Center: L. Harpole (98-0295), 1998-2004 (Box 39, Folder 270-273)
    - Duke University Medical Center: L. Harpole (98-0295): "IMPACT: Improving Care for Late Life Depression", 1999; 2014:023:001; Betacam: SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11147)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instructions.
  - Duke University Medical Center: H. Cohen (99-0339), 1999-2003 (Box 39, Folder 274)
  - Duke University Medical Center: H. Cohen (99-0339), 1999-2003 (Box 40, Folder 275-276)
  - Fallon Community Health Plan: J. Burl (99-0540), 1999-2003 (Box 40, Folder 277-279)
  - Foundation-Administered Project: Geriatric Social Work Initiative (99-0589), 1999-2003 (Box 40, Folder 280-282)
  - Foundation-Administered Project: Geriatric Social Work Initiative (99-0589), 1999-2003 (Box 41, Folder 283-291)
    - Foundation-Administered Project: Geriatric Social Work Initiative (99-0589): "Evaluation data for the JAHF GSWI", 2002; 2014:023:002; CD: Evaulation data. List of file titles accompanies disk. (Box 2014:023:002)
      Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
  - Foundation-Administered Project: Geriatric Social Work Initiative (99-0589), 1999-2003 (Box 42, Folder 292-293)
  - Florida Health Care Association, Education and Development Foundation: L. Polivka-West (2006-0172), 2006-2010 (Box 42, Folder 294-300)
  - Florida Health Care Association, Education and Development Foundation: L. Polivka-West (2006-0172), 2006-2010 (Box 43, Folder 301-303)
    - Florida Health Care Association, Education and Development Foundation: L. Polivka-West (2006-0172): "September 2007 Interim Report", 2014:023:003; CD-R: Interim report and attachments. PDF files (Box 2014:023:003)
  - George Washington University, National Health Policy Forum: J. Miller (97-0005), 1997-2000 (Box 43, Folder 304-307)
  - George Washington University, National Health Policy Forum: J. Miller (97-0005), 1997-2000 (Box 44, Folder 308-313)
  - George Washington University, National Health Policy Forum: J. Miller (97-0005), 1997-2000 (Box 45, Folder 314-316)
  - George Washington University: J. Miller Jones (99-0411), 1999-2002 (Box 45, Folder 317-321)
  - George Washington University: J. Miller Jones (99-0411), 1999-2002 (Box 46, Folder 322-323)
  - Gerontological Society of America: L. Harootyan (99-0006), 1999-2003 (Box 46, Folder 324-328)
  - Gerontological Society of America: L. Harootyan (99-0006), 1999-2003 (Box 47, Folder 329-333)
  - Gerontological Society of America: L. Harootyan (99-0006), 1999-2003 (Box 48, Folder 334-341)
  - Gerontological Society of America: L. Harootyan (99-0006), 1999-2003 (Box 49, Folder 342-346)
  - Gerontological Society of America: B. Berkman (2000-0264), 2000-2006 (Box 49, Folder 347)
  - Gerontological Society of America: B. Berkman (2000-0264), 2000-2006 (Box 50, Folder 348-353)
  - Gerontological Society of America: B. Berkman (2000-0264), 2000-2006 (Box 51, Folder 354-355)
  - Gerontological Society of America: J. Lubben (2000-0334), 2000-2007 (Box 51, Folder 356-360)
  - Gerontological Society of America: B. Berkman (2003-0169), 2003-2010 (Box 52, Folder 361-368)
  - Gerontological Society of America: B. Berkman (2003-0169), 2003-2010 (Box 53, Folder 369-370)
  - Gerontological Society of America: J. Lubben (2004-0078), 2004-2007 (Box 53, Folder 371)
  - Gerontological Society of America: B. Berkman (2004-0079), 2004-2010 (Box 53, Folder 372-373)
  - Geronotological Society of America: J. Lubben (2004-0210), 2004-2010 (Box 53, Folder 374-375)
  - Geronotological Society of America: J. Lubben (2004-0210), 2004-2010 (Box 54, Folder 376-378)
  - Gerontological Society of America: B. Berkman (2005-0044), 2005-2009 (Box 54, Folder 379-380)
  - Group Health Cooperative of Puget Sound: E. Wagner (2001-0006), 2001-2006 (Box 54, Folder 381-382)
  - Group Health Cooperative of Puget Sound: E. Wagner (2001-0006), 2001-2006 (Box 55, Folder 383)
  - The Health Human Services Planning Association: C. Bennett (99-0412), 1999-2001 (Box 55, Folder 384-385)
  - Hunter College: J. Ivry (99-0741), 1999-2004 (Box 55, Folder 386-389)
  - Hunter College: J. Ivry (99-0741), 1999-2004 (Box 56, Folder 390-392)
  - Indiana University: C. Callahan (98-0308), 1998-2004 (Box 56, Folder 393-395)
  - Institute of Medicine of the National Academies: C. Behney (2006-0133), 2006-2010 (Box 56, Folder 396)
  - Institute of Medicine of the National Academies: C. Behney (2006-0133), 2006-2010 (Box 57, Folder 397)
  - Johns Hopkins School of Medicine: J. Burton (94-0148), 1994-1999 (Box 57, Folder 398-403)
  - Johns Hopkins Bayview Medical Center: J. Burton (95-0309), 1995-1999 (Box 58, Folder 404-410)
  - Johns Hopkins Bayview Medical Center: J. Burton (95-0309), 1995-1999 (Box 59, Folder 411-412)
  - Johns Hopkins Bayview Medical Center: J. Burton (98-0309), 1998-2000 (Box 59, Folder 413-414)
  - Johns Hopkins University: J. Burton (99-0341), 1999-2005 (Box 59, Folder 415-417)
  - Kaiser Foundation Hospitals: R. Della Penna (97-0028), 1997-2001 (Box 60, Folder 418-422)
  - National PACE Association: S. Bloom (2000-0290), 2000-2004 (Box 60, Folder 423)
  - National PACE Association: S. Bloom (2000-0290), 2000-2004 (Box 61, Folder 424-428)
  - New York Academy of Medicine: P. Volland (99-0005), 1999-2003 (Box 61, Folder 429-430)
  - New York Academy of Medicine: P. Volland (99-0005), 1999-2003 (Box 62, Folder 431-432)
  - New York Academy of Medicine: P. Volland (2000-0052), 2000-2003 (Box 62, Folder 433-437)
  - New York Academy of Medicine: P. Volland (2000-0052), 2000-2003 (Box 63, Folder 438-440)
  - New York Academy of Medicine: P. Volland (2001-0622), 2001-2005 (Box 63, Folder 441-443)
  - New York University, NICHE: M. Mezey (95-0035), 1995-1999 (Box 63, Folder 444)
  - New York University, NICHE: M. Mezey (95-0035), 1995-1999 (Box 64, Folder 445-451)
  - New York University, NICHE: M. Mezey (95-0035), 1995-1999 (Box 65, Folder 452-457)
  - New York University, GITT: T. Fulmer (95-0228), 1995-1999 (Box 66, Folder 458-463)
  - New York University, GITT: T. Fulmer (95-0228), 1995-1999 (Box 67, Folder 464-469)
  - New York University, GITT: T. Fulmer (95-0228), 1995-1999 (Box 68, Folder 470-475)
  - New York University, GITT: T. Fulmer (95-0228), 1995-1999 (Box 69, Folder 476-482)
  - New York University, GITT: T. Fulmer (95-0228), 1995-1999 (Box 70, Folder 483-488)
  - New York University, GITT: T. Fulmer (95-0228), 1995-1999 (Box 71, Folder 489-491)
  - New York University, GITT: T. Fulmer (99-0003; extension of 95-0228), 1999-2001 (Box 71, Folder 492-493)
  - New York University, GITT: T. Fulmer (99-0003; extension of 95-0228), 1999-2001 (Box 72, Folder 494-496)
  - New York University, Nursing Institute: M. Mezey (95-0325), 1995-2002 (Box 72, Folder 497-502)
  - New York University, Nursing Institute: M. Mezey (95-0325), 1995-2002 (Box 73, Folder 503-509)
  - New York University, Nursing Institute: M. Mezey (95-0325), 1995-2002 (Box 74, Folder 510-515)
  - New York University, Nursing Institute: M. Mezey (95-0325), 1995-2002 (Box 75, Folder 516-521)
  - New York University, Nursing Institute: M. Mezey (95-0325), 1995-2002 (Box 76, Folder 522-528)
  - New York University, Nursing Institute: M. Mezey (95-0325), 1995-2002 (Box 77, Folder 529-535)
  - New York University, Nursing Institute: M. Mezey (95-0325), 1995-2002 (Box 78, Folder 536-537)
  - New York University, GITT: T. Fulmer (99-0003), 1999-2002 (Box 78, Folder 538-544)
  - New York University, GITT: T. Fulmer (2002-0030), 2002-2005 (Box 79, Folder 545-552)
  - New York University, GITT: T. Fulmer (2002-0030), 2002-2005 (Box 80, Folder 543-554)
  - New York University, How to Try This: M. Mezey (2006-0410), 2006-2010 (Box 80, Folder 555-558)
    - New York University, How to Try This: M. Mezey (2006-0410): "How To Try This" 1. Confusion Assessment Method, 2. Recognition of Dementia, circa 2010; 2014:023:004 (Box 2014:023:004)
    - New York University, How to Try This: M. Mezey (2006-0410): "How To Try This" 1. SPICES, 2. Geriatric Depression Scale - Short Form (Box 80)
  - New York University, Hartford Institute: M. Mezey (2007-0125), 2007-2010 (Box 80, Folder 559-561)
  - Omega of Palm Beach County: K. Rodriguez (2000-0420), 2000-2005 (Box 81, Folder 562-568)
  - Omega of Palm Beach County: K. Rodriguez (2000-0420), 2000-2005 (Box 82, Folder 569-576)
    - Omega of Palm Beach County: K. Rodriguez (2000-0420): "Jewish Seniors Focus Group", 2000 March 24; 2014:023:005; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11148)
    - Omega of Palm Beach County: K. Rodriguez (2000-0420): "Glades Seniors Focus Group", 2000 April 13; 2014:023:006; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11149)
    - Omega of Palm Beach County: K. Rodriguez (2000-0420): "Hispanic Seniors Focus Group" - Tape 1, 2000 April 13; 2014:023:007; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11150)
    - Omega of Palm Beach County: K. Rodriguez (2000-0420): "Hispanic Seniors Focus Group" - Tape 2, 2000 April 13; 2014:023:007; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11151)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Omega of Palm Beach County: K. Rodriguez (2000-0420), 2000-2005 (Box 83, Folder 577-578)
  - On Lok, Inc., ICCIS: J. Chin Hansen (96-0246), 1996-2001 (Box 83, Folder 579-583)
    - On Lok, Inc., ICCIS: J. Chin Hansen (96-0246): "ICCIS Training Demonstration", 1999 September 8; 2014:023:008; CD-R (Box 2014:023:008)
  - On Lok, Inc., ICCIS: J. Chin Hansen (96-0246), 1996-2001 (Box 84, Folder 584-585)
    - On Lok, Inc., ICCIS: J. Chin Hansen (96-0246): "ICCIS Source Code", 2001; 2014:023:009; Two CD-Rs: Documentation PDF file and Source Code CD (Box 2014:023:009)
    - On Lok, Inc., ICCIS: J. Chin Hansen (96-0246): "ICCIS Documentation PDF File" (Box 84)
  - On Lok, Inc.: J. Chin Hansen (2004-0206) (Box 84, Folder 586)
  - Partners in Care Foundation: W. J. Simmons (99-0725), 1999-2003 (Box 84, Folder 587-591)
  - Partners in Care Foundation: W. J. Simmons (99-0725), 1999-2003 (Box 85, Folder 592)
  - Partners in Care Foundation: W. J. Simmons (2001-0128), 2001-2004 (Box 85, Folder 593-596)
  - People-to-People Health Foundation: J. Iglehart (2001-0127), 2001-2003 (Box 85, Folder 597-598)
  - Portland VA Medical Center: S. Mader (99-0537), 1999-2004 (Box 85, Folder 599)
  - Portland VA Medical Center: S. Mader (99-0537), 1999-2004 (Box 86, Folder 600-601)
  - RAND Corporation: H. Pincus (2001-0349), 2001-2006 (Box 86, Folder 602-606)
  - RAND Corporation: H. Pincus (2001-0349), 2001-2006 (Box 87, Folder 607-609)
  - Society for Academic Emergency Medicine: A. Sanders (90-0286), 1990-1992 (Box 87, Folder 610-612)
  - Society for Academic Emergency Medicine: A. Sanders (90-0286), 1990-1992 (Box 88, Folder 613)
  - Society for Academic Emergency Medicine: A. Sanders (92-0212), 1992-1999 (Box 88, Folder 614-620)
  - Society for Academic Emergency Medicine: A. Sanders (92-0212), 1992-1999 (Box 89, Folder 621-626)
  - Society for Academic Emergency Medicine: A. Sanders (92-0212), 1992-1999 (Box 90, Folder 627-628)
  - Society of General Internal Medicine: K. Kroenke (2000-0190), 2000-2004 (Box 90, Folder 629-633)
  - Spartanburg Regional Medical Center: B. Whitney (97-0125), 1997-2003 (Box 91, Folder 634-639)
  - Spartanburg Regional Medical Center: B. Whitney (97-0125), 1997-2003 (Box 92, Folder 640-642)
  - State University of New York [SUNY], Albany: A. Fortune (99-0722), 1999-2004 (Box 92, Folder 643-645)
  - State University of New York [SUNY], Albany: A. Fortune (99-0722), 1999-2004 (Box 93, Folder 646)
  - State University of New York [SUNY], Albany: P. McCallion (2001-0118), 2001-2005 (Box 93, Folder 647-651)
  - Stanford University: G. Stratos (97-0301), 1997-2002 (Box 93, Folder 652-653)
  - Stanford University: G. Stratos (97-0301), 1997-2002 (Box 94, Folder 654-660)
  - Stanford University: G. Stratos (2004-0264), 2004-2005 (Box 94, Folder 661)
  - Southeast Center of Excellence in Geriatric Medicine: J. Ouslander (97-0273 and 97-0333), 1997-2002 (Box 95, Folder 662-667)
  - Southeast Center of Excellence in Geriatric Medicine: J. Ouslander (97-0273 and 97-0333), 1997-2002 (Box 96, Folder 668-669)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: R. Kane (84-0079), 1984-1986 (Box 96, Folder 670-674)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: J. Beck (85-0184), 1985-1988 (Box 97, Folder 675)
  - University of California, Los Angeles, GITT: J. Frank (96-0296), 1996-2001 (Box 97, Folder 676-681)
  - University of California, Los Angeles, GITT: J. Frank (96-0296), 1996-2001 (Box 98, Folder 682-687)
  - University of California: D. Reuben (99-0343), 1999-2004 (Box 99, Folder 688-690)
  - University of California, Berkeley: B. Robinson (99-0719), 1999-2005 (Box 99, Folder 691-694)
  - University of California, Berkeley: B. Robinson (99-0719), 1999-2005 (Box 100, Folder 695-696)
  - University of California, San Francisco: J. Kayser-Jones (2000-0095), 2000-2007 (Box 100, Folder 697-701)
  - University of California, San Francisco: J. Kayser-Jones (2000-0095), 2000-2007 (Box 101, Folder 702-706)
  - University of California, San Francisco: S. Landefeld (2000-0455), 2000-2004 (Box 101, Folder 707)
  - University of California, San Francisco: S. Landefeld (2000-0455), 2000-2004 (Box 102, Folder 708-710)
  - University of Chicago: G. Sachs (94-0155), 1994-1999 (Box 102, Folder 711-712)
  - University of Chicago: G. Sachs (94-0155), 1994-1999 (Box 103, Folder 713-714)
  - University of Chicago: G. Sachs (99-0590), 1999-2005 (Box 103, Folder 715-718)
  - University of Colorado: A. Kramer (2000-0429), 2000-2004 (Box 103, Folder 719-720)
  - University of Colorado: A. Kramer (2000-0429), 2000-2004 (Box 104, Folder 721)
  - University of Colorado: E. Coleman (2000-0443), 2000-2006 (Box 104, Folder 722-728)
    - The Care Transitions Intervention, 2005-2006; 2014:023:010 (Box 2014:023:010)
    - The Care Transitions Intervention: Appendix F, 2005 (Box 104)
  - University of Colorado: E. Coleman (2000-0443), 2000-2006 (Box 105, Folder 729-731)
  - University of Connecticut: G. Sullivan (94-0156), 1994-1999 (Box 105, Folder 732-734)
  - University of Hawaii: P. Blanchette (2000-0434), 2000-2005 (Box 105, Folder 735-737)
  - University of Hawaii: P. Blanchette (2000-0434), 2000-2005 (Box 106, Folder 738-739)
  - University of Houston: V. Cooke Robbins (99-0724), 1999-2004 (Box 106, Folder 740-744)
  - University of Houston: V. Cooke Robbins (99-0724), 1999-2004 (Box 107, Folder 745-748)
  - University of Iowa: M. Maas (2000-0088), 2000-2007 (Box 107, Folder 749)
  - University of Iowa: M. Maas (2000-0088), 2000-2007 (Box 108, Folder 750-756)
  - University of Iowa: M. Maas (2000-0088), 2000-2007 (Box 109, Folder 757-763)
  - University of Iowa: M. Maas (2000-0088), 2000-2007 (Box 110, Folder 764)